However,if it's observed after it's left the plane
But before it hits its target,
it won't have gone through both slits.
II1555Agreed.whats your point?XA 1
There's no point,I just think it's a good idea for a t-shirt.
excuse me. -hang on
One across is "aegean."
Eight down is "nabokov."
26 across is "mcm."
14 down is... move your finger.
"phylum" which makes 14 across "port-au-prince"
See,"papa doc's capitol idea," that's "port-au-prince."
Haiti.
-can I help you?-yes.
Is this the high-iq sperm bank?
If you have to ask,maybe you shouldn't be here.
I think this is theplace.
-fill these out. -thank you.
#
#  #
Leonard,I don't think I can do this.
What,are you kidding? you're a semi-pro.
No. we.are committing genetic fraud.
There's no guarantee that our sperm
is going to generate high-iqOffspring.
Think about that. I have a sister with the same basic dna mix
Who hostesses at-fuddruckers.
Sheldon,this was your idea.
A little extra money to get
fractional t-1 bandwidth in the apartment.
I know,and I do yearn for faster downloads.
But there's some poor woman
who's gonna pin her hopes on my sperm.
What if she winds up with a toddler who doesn't know if he should use
An integral or a differential to solve the area under a curve?
-i'm sure she'll still love him. -i wouldn't.
Well,what do you want to do?
I want to leave.
OK
What's the protocol for leaving?
I don't know.. I've never reneged on a proffer of sperm before
Let's try just walking out.
-bye. -bye. nice meeting you.
Are you still mad about the sperm bank?
No.
You want to hear an interesting thing about stairs?
Not really.
If the height of a single step is off by as little as two millimeters,
-most people will trip. -i don't care.
Two mili... that doesn't seem right.
No,it's true,I did a series of experiments when I was 12
My father broke his clavicle.
Is that why they sent you to boarding school?
No. that was a result of my work with lasers.
New neighbor?
Evidently.
Significant improvement over the old neighbor.
200-pound transvestite with a skin condition?
Yes,she is.
W-ohhi-hiK
=oh.hi.=hi.
rOLVCOCY
VOCV
We don't mean to interrupt. we live across the hall
Oh,that'snice.
We don't live together. I mean...
We live together,
But in separate,heterosexual bedrooms.
Okay:well..
Okay.well
Guess I'm your new neighbor. penny
-leonard. sheldon. -hi.
-hi. -hi.
Well..
Welcome to the building.
Thank you, maybe we can have coffee sometime.
Great.
-well.. bye. -bye.
bye.
Should we have invited her for lunch?
No.We're gonna start season two of battlestar galactica.
We already watched the season two dvds.
Not with commentary.
I think we should be good neighbors
And invite her over,make her feel welcome.
We never invited louie-slash-louise over.
And that was wrong of us.
We need to widen our circle.
I have a very wide circle.
I have 212 friends on myspace.
Yes,and you've never met one of them.
That's the beauty of it.
I'm gonna invite her over.
We'll have a nice meal and... chat.
Chat? we don't chat. at least not offline.
It's not difficult.
You just listen to what she says
And then you say something appropriate in response.
To what end?
Hi... again..
Hi.
Anyway..
We brought home indian food.
And..
I know that moving can be stressful
And I find that when I'm undergoing stress,
That good food and company can have a comforting effect.
Also curry is a natural laxative,and I don't have to tell you
That,you know,a clean colon is just.
One less thing to worry about.
I'm no expert,but I believe in the context of a luncheon invitation
You might want to skip the reference to bowel movements.
You're inviting me over to eat?
Yes.
Oh,that's so nice. I'd love to.
Great.
Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state
Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started. Wait!
The Earth began to cool
-TheEarth began-to cool,
The autotrophs began todrool-Neanderthals developed tools
Theautotiophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools
We built-the Wall We built the pyramids
We built-the Wall-We builtithe pyramids.
. That all started with a big bang
Bang!
BTTE
Okay,make yourself at home.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
This looks like some serious stuff.
-leonard,did you do this? actually,that's my work.
Yeah. wellit's just some quantum mechanics
With a little string theory doodling around the edges.
That part there,that's just a joke.
It's a spoof of the born-oppenheimer approximation.
So you're like one of those beautiful mind genius guys.
Yeah
-this is really impressive. -i have a board
If you like boards,this is my board.
Holy smokes.
If by "holy smokes".you mean
A derivative restatement of the kind of stuff
You can find scribbled on the wallof any men's room at mit,sure.
.1
-what? -come on.
Who hasn't seen this differential below "here I sit.broken-hearted?
At least I didn't have to invent 26 dimensions
Just to make the math come out.
#